
--- Security Service Check Report ---
Generated on 11/11/2025 07:20:19

Service SMTPSVC not found.

RemoteRegistry (Allows remote users to modify registry settings) - Status: Stopped
No action needed. RemoteRegistry is already secure.

Service FTPSVC not found.

TermService (Enables Remote Desktop) - Status: Stopped
No action needed. TermService is already secure.

Service irmon not found.

TapiSrv (Telephony Service) - Status: Stopped
No action needed. TapiSrv is already secure.

PlugPlay (Plug and Play Service) - Status: Running
Action: PlugPlay disabled and stopped for security.

SNMPTRAP (SNMP Trap Service) - Status: Stopped
No action needed. SNMPTRAP is already secure.

--- End of Report ---
